export default {
  id: 'low_1006_6_2b',
  name: '상용한자(6학년-2/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:そう/음:えん', answer: ['沿'] },
    { question: '독:うつ(る)、うつ(す)、は(える)/음:えい', answer: ['映'] },
    { question: '독:そ(める)、そ(まる)、し(みる)、し(み)/음:せん', answer: ['染'] },
    { question: '독:あやま(る)/음:ご', answer: ['誤'] },
    { question: '독:ほっ(する)、ほ(しい)/음:よく', answer: ['欲'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:う', answer: ['宇'] },
    { question: '독:우편/음:ゆう', answer: ['郵'] },
    { question: '독:やさ(しい)、すぐ(れる)/음:ゆう', answer: ['優'] },
    { question: '독:みなもと/음:げん', answer: ['源'] },
    { question: '독:あぶ(ない)、あや(うい)、あや(ぶむ)/음:き', answer: ['危'] },
    { question: '독:ちち、ち/음:にゅう', answer: ['乳'] },
    { question: '독:おさな(い)/음:よう', answer: ['幼'] },
    { question: '독:남길/음:い、[ゆい]', answer: ['遺'] },
    { question: '독:うたが(う)/음:ぎ', answer: ['疑'] },
    { question: '독:こと/음:い', answer: ['異'] },
    { question: '독:다음날/음:よく', answer: ['翌'] },
    { question: '독:みと(める)/음:にん', answer: ['認'] },
    { question: '독:어질/음:じん、[に]', answer: ['仁'] },
    { question: '독:품삯/음:ちん', answer: ['賃'] },
    { question: '독:すがた/음:し', answer: ['姿'] },
    { question: '독:자석/음:じ', answer: ['磁'] },
    { question: '독:かいこ/음:さん', answer: ['蚕'] },
    { question: '독:장수/음:しょう', answer: ['将'] },
    { question: '독:よそお(う)/음:そう、しょう', answer: ['装'] },
    { question: '독:くら/음:ぞう', answer: ['蔵'] },
    { question: '독:오장/음:ぞう', answer: ['臓'] },
    { question: '독:さわ(る)/음:しょう', answer: ['障'] },
    { question: '독:た(つ)、さば(く)/음:さい', answer: ['裁'] },
    { question: '독:あらわ(す)、いちじる(しい)/음:ちょ', answer: ['著'] },
    { question: '독:もっぱ(ら)/음:せん', answer: ['専'] },
    { question: '독:펼/음:てん', answer: ['展'] },
    { question: '독:いただ(く)、いただき/음:ちょう', answer: ['頂'] },
    { question: '독:す(む)、す(ます)/음:さい', answer: ['済'] },
    { question: '독:모두/음:しょ', answer: ['諸'] },
    { question: '독:のぞ(く)/음:じょ、[じ]', answer: ['除'] },
    { question: '독:みさお、あやつ(る)/음:そう', answer: ['操'] },
    { question: '독:しお/음:ちょう', answer: ['潮'] },
    { question: '독:있을/음:そん、ぞん', answer: ['存'] },
    { question: '독:とうと(い)、とうと(ぶ)、たっと(い)、たっと(ぶ)/음:そん', answer: ['尊'] },
    { question: '독:마루/음:しゅう、そう', answer: ['宗'] },
    { question: '독:したが(う)、したが(える)/음:じゅう、[しょう]、[じゅ]', answer: ['従'] },
    { question: '독:たて/음:じゅう', answer: ['縦'] },
    { question: '독:すわ(る)/음:ざ', answer: ['座'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:ちゅう', answer: ['宙'] },
    { question: '독:かぶ/음:しゅ', answer: ['株'] },
    { question: '독:かな(でる)/음:そう', answer: ['奏'] },
    { question: '독:무리/음:しゅう、[しゅ]', answer: ['衆'] },
    { question: '독:む(す)、む(れる)、む(らす)/음:じょう', answer: ['蒸'] },
    { question: '독:기록할/음:し', answer: ['誌'] },
    { question: '독:いた(る)/음:し', answer: ['至'] },
    { question: '독:まど/음:そう', answer: ['窓'] },
    { question: '독:비롯할/음:そう', answer: ['創'] },
    { question: '독:책/음:さつ、さく', answer: ['冊'] },
    { question: '독:꾀/음:さく', answer: ['策'] },
    { question: '독:곳/음:しょ', answer: ['処'] },
    { question: '독:자/음:しゃく', answer: ['尺'] },
    { question: '독:いずみ/음:せん', answer: ['泉'] },
    { question: '독:관청/음:ちょう', answer: ['庁'] },
    { question: '독:마디/음:すん', answer: ['寸'] },
    { question: '독:お(す)/음:すい', answer: ['推'] },
    { question: '독:ちぢ(む)、ちぢ(まる)、ちぢ(める)、ちぢ(れる)、ちぢ(らす)/음:しゅく', answer: ['縮'] },
    { question: '독:충성/음:ちゅう', answer: ['忠'] },
    { question: '독:つ(く)、つ(ける)/음:しゅう、[じゅ]', answer: ['就'] },
    { question: '독:층/음:そう', answer: ['層'] },
    { question: '독:ね、あたい/음:ち', answer: ['値'] },
    { question: '독:はり/음:しん', answer: ['針'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:たく', answer: ['宅'] },
    { question: '독:낳을/음:たん', answer: ['誕'] },
    { question: '독:さ(ぐる)、さ(がす)/음:たん', answer: ['探'] },
    { question: '독:うつ/음:とう', answer: ['討'] },
    { question: '독:いた(い)、いた(む)、いた(める)/음:つう', answer: ['痛'] },
    { question: '독:갈래/음:は', answer: ['派'] },
    { question: '독:かた/음:へん', answer: ['片'] },
    { question: '독:허파/음:はい', answer: ['肺'] },
    { question: '독:대궐섬돌/음:へい', answer: ['陛'] },
    { question: '독:し(まる)、し(める)、と(じる)、と(ざす)/음:へい', answer: ['閉'] },
    { question: '독:わ(る)、わり、わ(れる)、さ(く)/음:かつ', answer: ['割'] },
    { question: '독:시골/음:きょう、ごう', answer: ['郷'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:けん', answer: ['憲'] },
    { question: '독:かわ/음:かく', answer: ['革'] },
    { question: '독:あな/음:けつ', answer: ['穴'] },
    { question: '독:よ(ぶ)/음:こ', answer: ['呼'] },
    { question: '독:べに、くれない/음:こう、[く]', answer: ['紅'] },
    { question: '독:넓힐/음:かく', answer: ['拡'] },
    { question: '독:임금/음:こう、おう', answer: ['皇'] },
    { question: '독:はい/음:かい', answer: ['灰'] },
    { question: '독:효도/음:こう', answer: ['孝'] },
    { question: '독:きさき/음:こう', answer: ['后'] },
    { question: '독:휘두를/음:き', answer: ['揮'] },
    { question: '독:むね、[むな]/음:きょう', answer: ['胸'] },
    { question: '독:す(う)/음:きゅう', answer: ['吸'] }
  ]
}
